transnet.net 2019-12-08

# Transnet Transnet SOC Limited HR Privacy Statement

Transnet SOC Limited (hereafter referred to as "Transnet") will handle any and all personal information it obtains during the course of its recruitment activities, strictly in compliance with laws and regulations governing personal information. 

"Personal information", as in the context of this policy, refers to, regardless of the medium through which such information has been sent to Transnet, the following types of data, which have been directly or indirectly obtained during the course of recruitment activities by Transnet, and which enable the identification of any individual applicant and or candidate.

The range of personal information includes, but is not limited to:

  * Personal details and employment history and other items as input into the profile and or application 
  * Details of the communication made between Transnet and the applicant and or candidate for the purpose of recruitment activities 
  * Such other data that can easily be collated with other data and thereby enable the identification of the applicant and or candidate 

Transnet uses the applicant and or candidate's personal information for the purposes of providing them with recruitment information; screening for recruitment; and confirming their job application records. If an applicant and or candidate are employed by Transnet, his/her personal data will be continuously used for employee management purposes.

Companies belonging to Transnet and its Operating Divisions will jointly use the personal information of applicants and or candidates for the purposes set forth above.

Transnet undertakes to put in place appropriate safety control measures for personal information about applicants and or candidates it has gained, in order to prevent the risk of unlawful accesses, loss, alteration and disclosure thereof.

Transnet accepts, within reasonable limits, an employment applicant's requests for disclosure, amendment and deletion of his/her own personal information. However, Transnet is unable to accept any such requests concerning information related to the screening for employment, to avoid any possible consequence affecting Transnet proper and normal course of business operations. Any personal information of any applicants and or candidates retained by Transnet will, after the purposes of its use have been met, be either, destroyed or deleted by adequate measures.
